cardboardconnection.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from us, please fill out the subscription cancellation form located at http://community.cardboardconnection.com/cancel-subscription/..

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow), that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **eBay Advertisements**

Please note that The Cardboard Connection is an advertising affiliate of eBay, and that we get paid a small amount for each purchase made by individuals who click on our eBay affiliate links. We insert relevant eBay listings into many of our articles for the convenience of our readers using the following methods:

* Visual column-based, real-time listings inserted in various articles. These boxes carry the "Hot Deal Finder" logo in their top left-hand corners.  
* Various custom eBay widgets, all of which have the eBay logo attached to them.  
* Text links.  
o We link to eBay listings using a variety of affiliate text links, particularly in articles where we are covering major eBay auctions.  
o Due to repeated requests by fellow collectors to help them easily find deals on sports card wax products, we automatically link the titles of most sports card products to appropriate auction listings for the corresponding products on eBay. Clicking on the links will forward you to our custom-tailored product list on eBay's site.

Clicking on our affiliate links will not cause you, the end user, to incur any additional expense.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on August 2, 2009

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

The Cardboard Connection Sports Card and Memorabilia Report  
https://www.cardboardconnection.com  
1860 Sandy Plains Road, Ste 204-137  
Marietta, GA 30066  
United States

 **Check Out Our Exclusive Ranking Guides to:**
